Congratulations.
We've seen a lot of things so far.
So let's recap.
First of all, we saw in the first video that the LoRa modulation is a long distance and a low speed transmission.
By the way, the word long distance come from its name because LoRa stands for Long Range.
Then we saw that if we use LoRaWAN in Europe it transmits on channels belonging to
the 868 MHz band. And several end devices can transmit at the same time and on the same channel,
if each of them uses a different parameter called spreading factor. This spreading factor can be from
SF5 up to SF12.
If we use LoRaWAN, which will be the case in this lecture, there are only 6 spreading factors from SF7
to SF12.
I sometimes use the word LoRa and sometimes LoRaWAN.
But no worries,
there will be a dedicated video to explain the differences between the modulation and the protocol.
However, we will mainly speak about LoRaWAN later in this course.
So now in the next chapter, we are going to see what kind of performances we can expect for wireless
radio transmission and what terms we need to master to be comfortable with a technical documentation
about a LoRa end device.